Guide to the A. P. Watt and Son records, 1861-1971 [bulk 1880-1949]
The New York Public Library. Henry W. and Albert A. Berg Collection of English and American Literature.
- Correspondence, 517474
  - Incoming Correspondence, 517493
    - Kenyon, Sir Frederic George. ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1936 Mar. 14; 517689; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Kipling, Caroline (Balestier). 2 ALS (1 incomplete), 14 TLS, 1 telegram to A. P. Watt and son. Relate to Rudyard Kipling, 1909 May 4 - 1936 Feb. 23; 517690; in. corr.; 17 letters in 4 folders (Manuscript box)
      With extracts of 9 letters from Mrs. Kipling to Watt. Dec. 22, 1924-Mar. 23, 1937. 1 p. each; 37 TL (carbon) replies and 3 related memoranda; Thalberg, Irving. TLS to R. Kipling, July 9, 1931; Noyes, A. TL to Times editor, Feb. 15, 1936
    - Kipling, Rudyard. 2 ALS, 3 ANS, 3 TLS, 1 telegram to A. P. Watt and son, 1889 May 12 - 1935 May 21; 517691; in. corr.; 9 letters in 2 folders (Manuscript box)
      With Watt's "Notes of conversation with Mr. and Mrs. Kipling, Jan. 24, 1929." 1 p.
    - Knox, Ronald A. TLS to A. P. Watt and son, n.y.] May 24; 517692; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Konstam, Edwin Max. ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1902 Aug. 8; 517693; in. corr.; 2 p (Manuscript box)
      Accompanied by: Bunting, Percy Wiliam. ANS to A. P. Watt and son. Aug. 1, 1902. 1 p.
    - Lang, Louisa Lockhart (Steuart). ALS to [A. P. Watt and son], 1908] Aug. 8; 517694; in. corr.; 1 leaf (Manuscript box)
    - László de Lombos, Phlip Alexius. TLS to A. P. Watt and son, 1936 Jan. 16; 517695; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Law, Richard Kidston. TNS to A. P. Watt and son, 1939 Nov. 2; 517696; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Leacock, Stephen Butler. ANS to A. P. Watt and son, 1916 Oct. 1; 517697; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Leisure Hour. 3 letters to A. P. Watt and son, 1885 Oct. 26 - 1885 Oct. 29; 517698; in. corr.; 3 leaves; 3 p.; 1 leaf (Manuscript box (Oliphant))
      Signed William Stevens. With related letter to Watt from The Religious tract society, Oct. 23, 1885. 1 p.
    - Le Queux, William Tufnell. 2 ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1900 Mar. 12; [1913] May 23; 517699; in. corr.; 3 leaves; 3 p (Manuscript box)
      With Watt's TL (copy) reply, May 22, 1913. Letter of May 23 [1913] encloses ANS from F. V. White to Le Queux, May 22, 1913
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Blanche Elizabeth Campbell Balfour Dugdale. Relate to Mrs. Dugdale's biography of her uncle, Arthur James Balfour, 1st earl of Balfour, 1931 - 1935; 517700; in. corr.; 39 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Balfour))
      Includes TLS from Harold Macmillan, May 17, 1935. 1 p.
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Sabine Baring-Gould, 1886 - 1887; 517701; in. corr.; 11 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Baring-Gould))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for John Hay Beith, 1933; 517702; in. corr.; 35 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Beith))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Sir Walter Besant, 1884 - 1909; 517703; in. corr.; 48 letters in 4 folders (Manuscript box (Besant, W.))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various correspondents, not listed separately, to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for the Palestine Exploration Fund. Sir Walter Besant was secretary of the Palestine Exploration Fund, 1885 - 1886; 517704; in. corr.; 25 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Besant, W.))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Max O'Rell [pseudonym of Paul Blouet], 1887; 517705; in. corr.; 2 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Blouet))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for John Buchan, 1916; 517706; in. corr.; 2 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Buchan))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Sir Winston Churchill, 1944; 517707; in. corr.; 4 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Churchill, W. S.))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Frances Dunn Collins, 1880; 517708; in. corr.; 6 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Collins, F. D.))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Wilkie Collins, 1881 - 1898; 517709; in. corr.; 120 letters in 8 folders (Manuscript box (Collins, Wilkie))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Samuel Rutherford Crockett, 1899 - 1916; 517710; in. corr.; 2 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Crockett))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Louise de la Ramé, 1884 - 1885; 517711; in. corr.; 4 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (De la Ramé))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Sir Arthur Conan Doyle, 1896 - 1914; 517712; in. corr.; 4 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Doyle, A. C.))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Charles Garvice, 1920 - 1926; 517713; in. corr.; 11 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Garvice))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Sir Henry Rider Haggard, 1887 - 1914; 517714; in. corr.; 12 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Haggard))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Bret Harte, 1885 - 1886; 517715; in. corr.; 7 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Harte))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Sir Anthony Hope Hawkins, 1914; 517716; in. corr.; 2 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Hawkins, A. H.))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as publisher of Health, 1888; 517717; in. corr.; 3 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Watt, A. P.))
      With 7 statements to Health accounts, April - June 1886
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Jean Ingelow, 1880; 517718; in. corr.; 19 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Ingelow))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Harriet Jay, 1880 - 1881; 517719; in. corr.; 11 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Jay, H.))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Edward Jenkins, 1880 - 1881; 517720; in. corr.; 26 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Jenkins, E.))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Sir Harry Hamilton Johnston, 1902; 517721; in. corr.; 1 letter (Manuscript box (Johnston, H. H.))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Rudyard Kipling, 1899 - 1940; 517722; in. corr.; 20 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Kipling))
      With 17 TL (carbon) replies and 4 memoranda
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for William Tufnell Le Queux, 1899 - 1913; 517723; in. corr.; 3 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Le Queux))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Edward Robert Bulwer-Lytton, 1st earl of Lytton, 1891 - 1892; 517724; in. corr.; 5 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Lytton, E. R. B.-L.))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for George MacDonald, 1882 - 1887; 517725; in. corr.; 3 letters (Manuscript box (MacDonald, G.))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for William Somerset Maugham, 1947 - 1956; 517726; in. corr.; 14 letters (Manuscript box (Maugham))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son relating to Cecil William Mercer, 1935 - 1937; 517727; in. corr.; 4 letters (Manuscript box (Mercer))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for James Eric Drummond, 16th earl of Perth, 1939; 517728; in. corr.; 2 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Perth))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for the Literary Trustees of John Ruskin, 1914; 517729; in. corr.; 14 letters in 2 folder (Manuscript box (Ruskin))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for William Dundas Scott-Moncrieff, 1880 - 1881; 517730; in. corr.; 7 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Scott-Moncrieff, W. D.))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Jules Verne. Letter of Aug. 16, 1880 mentions G. A. Henty, 517731; in. corr.; 2 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Verne))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for unidentified authors, 1880 - 1937; 517732; in. corr.; 72 letters in 3 folders (Manuscript box (Watt, A. P.))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from unidentified authors to the firm of A. P. Watt and son, 1908 - 1935; 517733; in. corr.; 8 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Watt, A. P.))
    - Letters, ALS, TLS, etc. from miscellaneous correspondents, not listed separately, to the firm of A. P. Watt and son, 517734; in. corr.; 4 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Watt, A. P.))
    - Letters, ALS, telegrams, etc. from various publishers, etc. to the firm of A. P. Watt and son as literary agent for Herbert George Wells, 1926 - 1931; 517735; in. corr.; 13 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Wells))
      With carbons of 12 related letters from Watt
    - Lewis, Randolph. 2 telegrams to A. P. Watt and son. Relate to film versions of Rudyard Kipling's works, 1924 Oct. 16; 1924 Oct. 25; 517736; in. corr.; 1 p. each (Manuscript box (Kipling))
      With Watt's two carbon replies and four memoranda, and four TLS from Field Roscoe & Co. to Watt
    - Lindbergh, Charles Augustus. TNS to A. P. Watt and son, 1937 June 4; 517737; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Lindsay, Philip. TLS to A. P. Watt and son, 1934 Mar. 7; 517738; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Lindsay, Sir Ronald Charles. TLS to A. P. Watt and son, 1939 May 10; 517739; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
      With carbons of two letters from Watt, April 25 and May 19, 1939. 2 p.; 1 p.
    - Little, James Stanley. 15 ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1886 Feb. 30 - 1886 Dec. 23; 517740; in. corr.; 15 letters in 3 folders (Manuscript box (Watt, A. P.))
    - Livingston, Flora V. 4 TLS to A. P. Watt and son. Relate to her Rudyard Kipling bibliography, 1924 Jan. 4 - 1924 July 5; 517741; in. corr.; 2 p.; 2 p.; 1 p.; 1 p (Manuscript box (Kipling, R.))
      With related TLS from Field, Roscoe & co. to Watt, Jan. 12, 1925, and TL (copy) from Watt to Livingston, Dec. 3, 1940
    - London, Jack. 2 TLS, 1 telegram to A. P. Watt and son, 1906 June 24 - 1907 June 9; 517742; in. corr.; 2 p.; 1 p.; 1 telegram (Manuscript box)
      With typed copy of letter from Watt, May 10, 1907
    - Longman, Charles James. 2 ALS, 1 ANS, 1 TLS to A. P. Watt and son. Relate to Sir Henry Rider Haggard, 1887 May 5 - 1894 Mar. 16; 517743; in. corr.; 3 p.; 2 leaves; 1 p.; 2 p (Manuscript box (Haggard))
      With TL (carbon) reply, Nov. 24, 1898
    - Low (Sampson) Marston & co., Ltd. 13 TL, 3 TN to A. P. Watt and son. Relate to Jeffery Farnol, 1926 Jan. 27 - 1930 Aug. 29; 517744; in. corr.; 16 letters in 4 folders (Manuscript box (Farnol))
      With 8 TL (carbon) replies and 14 miscellaneous pieces
    - Lucoque, H[--?] L[--?]. 10 TLS to A. P. Watt and son. Relate to T. A. Guthrie, Sir W. A. Raleigh, Sir F. C. Burnand and others, 1914 Jan. 3 - 1914 July 21; 517745; in. corr.; 10 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Watt, A. P.))
    - Lytton, Edith (Williers) Bulwer-Lytton, countess of. 3 ALS to [A. P. Watt and son]. Relate to her husband, Edward Robert Bulwer-Lytton, 1st earl of Lytton, 1890 May 5 - [1892] Mar. 24; 517746; in. corr.; 1 leaf; 1 leaf; 1 p (Manuscript box (Lytton, E. R. B.-L.))
    - Lytton, Edward Robert Bulwer-Lytton, 1st earl of. 35 ALS, 1 LS, 2 telegrams to A. P. Watt and son, 1889 Jan. 18 - 1891 Feb. 7; 517747; in. corr.; 38 letters in 8 folders (Manuscript box)
      With A. S. Watt's ALS (copy) reply, Aug. 15, 1889. 3 p.
    - Macbeth, Robert Walker. 2 ALS to A. P. Watt and son. Relate to W. D. Cott-Moncrieff's The abdication, 1881 Jan. 22; 1881 Feb. 24; 517748; in. corr.; 1 p.; 2 p (Manuscript box (Scott-Moncrieff, W. D.))
    - MacDonald, George. 2 ALS, 1 ANS to A. P. Watt and son. Feb. 28, 1898 letter dated from received stamp, 1888] Nov. 10 - [1898 Feb. 28; 517749; in. corr.; 3 p.; 2 leaves; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - MacDonald, Greville. 2 ALS to A. P. Watt and son. Writer is the son of George MacDonald, 1908 Dec. 5; 1935 May 18; 517750; in. corr.; 2 leaves; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Kindersley, Emily Grace (Seely). TLS to A. P. Watt and son, 1936 July 25; 517751; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
      With: MacDonald, James Ramsay. TL, signed with stamp, to John Edward Bernard Seely, 1st baron Mottistone, July 22, 1936. 1 p.
    - Macdonald, Malcolm. TLS to A. P. Watt and son, 1936 Feb. 22; 517752; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - McKenna, Reginald. TNS to A. P. Watt and son, 1936 Sept. 21; 517753; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Macmillan, Harold. TLS to A. P. Watt and son, 1927 Mar. 8; 517754; in. corr.; 2 p (Manuscript box (Kipling))
      With 2 related Watt memoranda, Feb. 25, 1927; April 5, 1935. 1 p. each. Relate to Medici Society publication of Rudyard Kipling's works
    - Macmillan, Harold. TLS, TNS to A. P. Watt and son. Relate to W. S. Maugham's proposed selection of Rudyard Kipling's stories, 1951 Feb. 6; 1951 Feb. 21; 517755; in. corr.; 1 p. each (Manuscript box (Maugham))
    - Macmillan & Co., Ltd., London. Letter to A. P. Watt & son. Relates to Henry James' The Tragic Muse, 1890 Apr. 2; 517756; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box (James, H.))
    - McNeile, Herman Cyril. ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1916 May 11; 517757; in. corr.; 1 leaf (Manuscript box)
    - McNeile, Herman Cyril. ALS to A. P. Watt and son, n.y.] Feb. 19; 517758; in. corr.; 1 leaf (Manuscript box)
    - McNeile, Herman Cyril. TLS to A. P. Watt and son, n.y.] May 22; 517759; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Maffey & Brennall, solicitors, London. 37 TLS, 5 TNS to A. P. Watt and son. Relate to Marie Corelli and Bertha Vyver, 1925 July 28 - 1945 Feb. 16; 517760; in. corr.; 42 letters in 4 folders (Manuscript box (Corelli))
    - Mann, Mary E. (Rackham). ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1904 Mar. 26; 517761; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Marchmont, Arthur Williams. ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1901 Oct. 4; 517762; in. corr.; 3 p (Manuscript box)
    - Marks, Henry Kingdon. ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1936 Nov. 4; 517763; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
      With carbons of two letters from Watt, Oct. 23 and Nov. 5, 1936. 1 p. each
    - Marriott, Charles. ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1909 Mar. 24; 517764; in. corr.; 2 p (Manuscript box)
    - Marshall, Archibald. 3 ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1928 Oct. 2 - 1929 Dec. 19; 517765; in. corr.; 1 p. each (Manuscript box)
      With 2 TL (copy) replies and 2 related memoranda. Relate to filming stories by Rudyard Kipling
    - Masefield, John. ANS to A. P. Watt and son, 1919 June 22; 517766; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Mason, Alfred Edward Woodley. 2 ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1917 Mar. 13; [n.y.] Nov. 4; 517767; in. corr.; 1 p.; 2 p (Manuscript box)
    - Mathews, Basil Joseph. TNS to A. P. Watt and son, 1935 May 24; 517768; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Maugham, Frederic Herbert Maugham, 1st viscount. ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1937 Feb. 8; 517769; in. corr.; 1 leaf (Manuscript box)
    - Maugham, William Somerset. 10 ALS, 123 TLS, 1 telegram to A. P. Watt and son, 1947 Jan. 18 - 1964 May 9; 517770; in. corr.; 134 letters in 27 folders (Manuscript box)
      Enclosed in July 12, 1953: Ferry, Felix. TLS to Maugham. July 1, 1953. 2 p.; With AL (draft), signed W. P. Watt, TL, signed Patricia Butler, and 15 TL (carbons) from Watt to Maugham
    - Maxwell, Edward H. 4 ALS to A. P. Watt and son. Relate to the estate of writer's mother, Mary Elizabeth Braddon, 1915 Mar. 11 - 1915 Apr. 16; 517771; in. corr.; 2 leaves; 3 p.; 2 p.; 3 p (Manuscript box (Braddon))
      With 2 TLS from M. M. Westcott; TNS from Hodder & Stoughton, enclosing "List of plates of Miss Braddon's novels"; Watt's notes on an interview with Maxwell; and notes "Re valuation of Miss Braddon's copyrights [etc]".
    - Maxwell, Henry. ALS to A. P. Watt and son. Relates to The Naked truth by the writer's father, W. B. Maxwell, 1942 Nov. 7; 517772; in. corr.; 3 p (Manuscript box (Maxwell, W. B.))
    - Maxwell, J. & R., firm, publishers, London. 2 LS, 2 NS to A. P. Watt and son. Relate to Sir H. R. Haggard, 1886 Feb. 23 - 1887 May 24; 517773; in. corr.; 2 p.; 1 p.; 1 p.; 1 p (Manuscript box (Haggard))
      With Watt's reply (copy), Oct. 12, 1886. 1 p.
    - Maxwell, William Babington. ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1916 Feb. 17; 517774; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Maxwell, William Babington. ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1935 May 17; 517775; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Maxwell, William Babington. ANS to A. P. Watt and son, 1935 May 21; 517776; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Meeûs, Marie Louise (Egerton Castle), comtesse de. ALS, ANS to A. P. Watt and son, 1935 May 18; [n.d; 517777; in. corr.; 1 leaf; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Menzies, Allan. ANS to A. P. Watt and son, 1900 Oct. 3; 517778; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Mercer, Cecil William. 3 TNS to A. P. Watt and son, 1935 Aug. 11 - 1937 Oct. 31; 517779; in. corr.; 1 p. each (Manuscript box)
      With 3 TL (carbon) replies
    - Merrick, Leonard. ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1920 June 27; 517780; in. corr.; 2 p (Manuscript box)
      Printed in Letters addressed to A. P. Watt and his sons 1883-1924. London: A. P. Watt and sons, 1924, p. 140-141
    - Methuen, Sir Algernon Methuen Marshall, 1st bart. TLS to A. P. Watt and son. Relates to Frances Marion Parkinson Gostling, 1908 Feb. 28; 517781; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box (Gostling))
    - Methuen & Co., Ltd., London. 2 TL to A. P. Watt and son. Relate to Beatrice Harraden and others, 1905 Sept. 25; 1906 Sept. 19; 517782; in. corr.; 1 p. each (Manuscript box (Harraden))
      Signed Sir Algernon Methuen Marshall Methuen
    - Methuen & Co., Ltd., London. TL to A. P. Watt and son. Relates to Robert Smythe Hichens, 1907 July 15; 517783; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box (Hichens))
      Signed Sir Algernon Methuen Marshall Methuen. With Methuen & Co., ltd., London. 2 TN to A. P. Watt and son. March 2 and 4, 1908
    - Methuen & Co., Ltd., London. TN to A. P. Watt and son. Relates to Robert Smythe Hichens, 1908 Mar. 2; 517784; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box (Hichens))
      Signed George E. Webster. With Methuen & Co., ltd., London. TL and TN to A. P. Watt and son. July 15, 1907 and March 4, 1908
    - Methuen & Co., Ltd., London. TN to A. P. Watt and son. Relates to Robert Smythe Hichens. Mentions Maurice Hewlett, 1908 Mar. 4; 517785; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box (Hichens))
      Signed George E. Webster. With Methuen & Co., ltd., London. TL and TN to A. P. Watt and son. July 15, 1907 and March 2, 1908
    - Methuen & Co., Ltd., London. TL to A. P. Watt and son. Relates to Marie Corelli, 1916 Feb. 10; 517786; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box (Corelli))
      Signed George Webster
    - Milne, Alan Alexander. 4 ALS, 1 ANS to A. P. Watt and son, 1915 Sept. 20 - 1928 Dec. 15; 517787; in. corr.; 5 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box)
      With 2 ANS from his secretary, Celia Brice, to Watt
    - Milner, Violet. TLS, TNS to A. P. Watt and son, 1933 Feb. 11; 1935 May 24; 517788; in. corr.; 1 p. each (Manuscript box)
    - [Montgomery, Leslie Alexander]. Postcard to A. P. Watt and son, 1921 Dec. 21; 517789; in. corr.; 1 card (Manuscript box)
      Signed Lynn Doyle [pseud.]
    - Montgomery-Massingberd, Sir Archibald Armar. ALS to A. P. Watt and son. Relates to Archibald Percival Wavell, 1941] Dec. 6; 517790; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
      With carbons of two letters from Watt, Dec. 4 and 9, 1941. 1 p. each
    - Morrison, Herbert Stanley. TNS to A. P. Watt and son, 1935 Dec. 4; 517791; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Morten, Cutler & Co., London. 5 LS to A. P. Watt and son. Relate to Sir H. R. Haggard and W. A. Wills, 1894 Apr. 26 - 1894 May 31; 517792; in. corr.; 5 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box (Haggard))
    - Munro, Neil. 4 ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1900 June 26 - 1902 July 1; 517793; in. corr.; 1 p. each (Manuscript box)
    - Murray, David Christie. 5 ALS, 1 telegram to A. P. Watt and son, 1886 Oct. 13 - 1887 Feb. 7; 517794; in. corr.; 6 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box)
    - Murray, David Leslie. TLS to A. P. Watt and son. Relates to Kathleen Muriel Eyles, 1935 May 23; 517795; in. corr.; 2 p (Manuscript box)
    - Newbolt, Sir Henry John. ALS, ANS to A. P. Watt and son, 1922 Apr. 10; 1935 May 24; 517796; in. corr.; 1 leaf; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Newnes, George, Ltd., London. TL to A. P. Watt and son. Relates to Marie Corelli, 1905 Sept. 22; 517797; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box (Corelli))
      Encloses royalty statement for period ending June 30, 1905. 1 p.; From the files of A. P. Watt and son
    - Nicholson, Ivor. TNS to A. P. Watt and son. Relates to Isabel Constance Clarke, 1932 Feb. 23; 517798; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box (Clarke, I. C.))
    - Noyes, Alfred. ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1913 Sept. 22; 517799; in. corr.; 3 p (Manuscript box)
    - Noyes, Alfred. ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1935 May 20; 517800; in. corr.; 1 leaf (Manuscript box)
    - Noyes, Alfred. AL (incomplete) to A. P. Watt and son, 1938 Mar. 10; 517801; in. corr.; 2 leaves (Manuscript box)
      Encloses his: ALS to Herbert Edward Palmer. March 10, 1938. 1 leaf; with carbon of letter from Watt, Sept. 18, 1913. 1 p.
    - O'Brien, Kate. ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1932 Mar. 11; 517802; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - O'Connor, Frank. TLS to A. P. Watt and son, 1931] Oct. 10; 517803; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Oliphant, Margaret Oliphant Wilson. 4 ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1885] Nov. 13; 517804; in. corr.; 4 letters in 1 folder (Manuscript box)
    - Onions, Oliver [pseud.]. TLS to A. P. Watt and son, 1904 Mar. 28; 517805; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)
    - Orczy, Emma Magdalena Rosalia Maria Josefa Barbara, baroness. ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1909 July 25; 517806; in. corr.; 2 p (Manuscript box)
    - Orczy, Emma Magdalena Rosalia Maria Josefa Barbara, baroness. Postcard to A. P. Watt and son, 1917 Nov. 5; 517807; in. corr.; 1 card (Manuscript box)
    - Orczy, Emma Magdalena Rosalia Maria Josefa Barbara, baroness. ALS to A. P. Watt and son, 1918 Aug. 13; 517808; in. corr.; 1 p (Manuscript box)